KOMAL SAINI

CONTENT AND MARKETING

CONTACT INFO

- +91-9351387455
- komal991223@gmail.com
- Churu, Rajasthan, India
- upwork.com/komalsaini
- fiverr.com/komalsaini115
- in linkedin.com/komalsaini23

EDUCATION

2021-2023

MSc in Computer Science **MGS University**

2020-2021

Diploma in Event Management, **IGNOU University**

2017-2020

BSc in Maths **MGS University**

LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

HOBBY





Presentation Desgining

SUMMARY

Editor/Writer possesses 1 years experience in educational content writing/editing, content project management, content quality checking, B2B/B2C content writing, content team leading, freelancers, and blogging looking for the job of Content Manager in any reputed E-Commerce / Publishing in researching and documenting sources Excellent communication and interpersonal skills. Knowledge of various blog platforms like Blogger and WordPress

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS



EXPERIENCE

Hyggelit Private Limited, Content and Marketing, 2021-2022 ♂

- Developed and executed marketing strategies to increase brand awareness and drive sales.
- Created and managed content for various marketing channels, including social media, email marketing, and website.
- · Conducted market research and analysed data to identify trends and optimise marketing campaigns.

Aashman foundation, HR Executive, 2021-2022 ♂

- · Assisted in the recruitment process, including sourcing candidates and conducting interviews.
- Managed employee records and handled various administrative tasks, including employee onboarding and offboarding.
- · Coordinated employee training programs and facilitated teambuilding activities.

STRENGTHS

- Multitasking Skillsspan>
- Commited to Lifelong Learning
- Calm in fast Paced Environment
- Strong communication and interpersonal skills
- Proficient in Microsoft Office and Adobe Creative Suite
- Knowledgeable in various social media platforms

CERTIFICATES

- Internship certificate ♂
- Letter of Recommendation ☑
- Google Digital Marketing